Join us.
Together is a horror, romance film directed by Michael Shanks.
Years into their relationship, Tim and Millie find themselves at a crossroads as they move to
the country, abandoning all that is familiar in their lives except each other.
With tensions already flaring, a nightmarish encounter with a mysterious, unnatural
force threatens to corrupt their lives, their love, and their flesh.
Tim, played by Dave Franco.
Millie, played by Alison Brie.
Jamie, played by Damon Herriman.
Cath, played by Mia Morrissey.
Jordy, played by Karl Richmond.
Luke, played by Jack Kenny.
Together is a 2025 supernatural body horror film written and directed by
Michael Shanks in his feature-length directorial debut.
It stars Dave Franco and Alison Brie as a couple who move to the
countryside, where they encounter a mysterious force.
A co-production between Australia and the United States, Together premiered at Sundance on January 26, 2025, and
was released in the United States by Neon on July 30 and in Australia by Kismet Movies on July 31.
It received positive reviews from critics and grossed $32 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of countryside, musician, cave, cult, woods.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.